Why is it our responsibility to take care of everyone?
When did indigenous people take care of everyone in human history?
We literally have a planet because of indigenous people.
It is literally indigenous knowledge that has cared for the planet and sustained the earth.
So when did they?
They do, like right now.
Also, we are African.
African, black folks, we are of the original indigenous people.
And then we came here and we had to form a new indigeneity of black American.
And that is its own indigenous.
It is new.
We only been here a couple hundred years.
So this first question, why is it our responsibility to take care of everyone?
It's everyone's responsibility to take care of everyone.
You don't think it's your responsibility because you have disconnected from your indigeneity.
You want to think like a colonizer, even though you'll never have the benefits of being one.
Also, since when does caring about people mean you're having to take care of them?
You can't be an asshole and be dumb.
It's just, it's too lethal of a combination.
DC and Baltimore, you're up next.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book and get it signed.
RSVP at AmandaSeals.com